<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bible Notify</string>
    <string name="main_screen_title">Bible Notify</string>
    <string name="reader_screen_title">l'Ambon</string>
    <string name="notification_title">Lecture d'un livre des Écritures</string>
    <string name="bottom_text">Bible Notify © 2024 Contributeurs de Bible Notify</string>
    <string name="settings_screen_title">Paramètres</string>
    <string name="time_picker_text">Envoyer une notification quotidienne à:</string>
    <string name="license">Bible Notify © 2024 Contributeurs de Bible Notify.\n\n

        Licence: 
        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.\n

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.\n

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see [https://www.gnu.org/licenses].\n\n

        Additionally, you must remove all references to \"Bible Notify\" and \"Correct Syntax\"
        if you release an app based on the Bible Notify open source project.
        Including the apps package name, as this is reserved for the official app.</string>
    <string name="help_text">Bible Notify envoie des versets de manière quotidienne sous forme de notification. La notification permet d\'accéder au chapitre dont est tiré le verset.\n\n  Les textes de la Bible présents sur cette application sont tirés de la Bible de la liturgie, et reproduits avec l\'accord de l\'Association Episcopale Liturgique pour les pays Francophones - pour toute question ou demande, rendez-vous sur www.aelf.org. </string>
    <string name="visit_our_website">Le site de Bible Notify</string>
    <string name="close_text">Fermer</string>
    <string name="view_license">Licence</string>
    <string name="StartButton">Commencer à envoyer des notifications</string>
    <string name="ChangeTimeButton">Changer l\'heure des notifications</string>
    <string name="SetTimeButton">Définir l\'heure ici :</string>
    <string name="CancelButton">Annuler</string>
    <string name="info_button">Info</string>
    <string name="languages_button">Langues</string>
    <string name="languages_text">Langue:</string>

</resources>